Pioneer LDC , Nikkatsu , Oz , Xanadeux , Kadokawa Shoten , Tokyo Theatre .
An Oz Production
Ju-On : a curse born of someone who dies in the grip of powerful rage .
It gathers in the places frequented by that person in their life ,
working its spell on those who come into contact with it
and thus creating itself anew .
It 's 12 : 27 on Saturday morning .
This is Hideshima Fumiko with J-Line Midnight Angle .
Tonight 's theme is the wintry sea . I went to the sea in Okinawa recently .
When there 's nobody around , the seaside is lonelier than I thought .
But I went to the aquarium and saw a big ...
Hey , what 's going on ?
Just switch it off , will you ?
You .
This was a total eclipse of the moon .
Just stop it , Masashi .
You 're in such a bad mood . Did something happen ?
Nothing in particular .
What kind of role did you have today ?
It 's not even a role . I just had to act dead .
He said , " For the actress who dreams of becoming the queen of horror . "
Since when have I wanted to be the queen of horror ?
Plenty of actors on the agency 's books don 't have work .
You said so yourself .
My mother checks out all the shows you 're in .
- Your mother ? - Yeah .
The fact that her son 's fiancée is on TV is really something to boast about .
And what about the baby ? Have you told the agency about it ?
You can 't hide it forever . And we have a due date now .
I know !
Do you know what ? I ...
What was that ?
- l think we hit something . - What ?
It 's a cat .
What ?
Well , let 's go .
But ...
lt just jumped out of nowhere .
Masashi ? Masashi !
Ju-On : The Grudge 2
Kyoko
Take care .
How is Masashi ?
There 's no change at the moment .
I 'm so sorry that Kyoko was injured because of my son .
There 's nothing to apologise for .
Kyoko. I 'm so sorry you lost the baby .
I 'm really sorry .
Kaori . Kaori , pull yourself together .
Kaori , I think you should rest .
I 'm sorry .
Masashi .
It 's cold .
You must be tired . Have a sip of this and go to bed .
Mum , did I have any siblings ?
- What ? - Like a brother who died in childhood ?
A boy ?
What are you talking about ? You 're my only child .
Right .
In my family , we were all girls . Your baby will probably ...
lt was probably a girl .
I 'm sure it was a boy .
They 're beautiful .
Thanks , Kyoko .
I wonder if he 'll ever wake up .
- Teacher ... - Who 's there ?
It 's your fault .
And cut !
You scared me . What 's wrong with you ? The script doesn 't say scream .
You 're only an extra . Don 't do things you 're not told to do .
Chiharu ? Chiharu
We 'll take a break now . We 'll continue from scene 27 .
Please go for lunch .
- Thank you . - Chiharu ?
- Chiharu ! - What happened ?
Kawate ! Call Kawate !
Kawate !
It 's been three and a half months now .
It 's doing well .
Doctor ...
ls there anything wrong ?
Oh , you 're back . You scared me .
- l 'm back . - Welcome home .
is there anything wrong ?
Kyoko .
Mum ?
Mum . You 'll catch a cold .
Come on , Mum .
Mum ?
Hey , Mum !
Answer me .
Mum ! Hey , Mum !
Mum !
Tomoka
Years ago , the incident was reported about on TV and in the newspapers ...
Reported about on TV and in newspapers ... The incident was ...
The incident was reported about on TV and in the newspapers . A woman ...
What is it ?
What 's going on ?
Have you heard about the special programme ?
- Which one ? Keisuke 's ? - Yeah .
- Are you going to work on it too ? - l 'm getting fed up with that series .
I just think , " Not again ! "
Speaking of that , do you know who the guest star is ?
The guest ?
It 's an actress called ...
Harase Kyoko .
- Harase Kyoko , the horror queen ? - That 's right . You like horror .
- Tomoka . - Good morning .
Good morning . There you are .
Where is it this time ?
They found the rumoured haunted house in Nerima. lt 's an old family house .
Several people living there actually died .
A Real Haunted House - The Mysterious Deaths
I 'm not going to do anything like what we did before .
What 's that ?
- You played the ghost really well . - Did you play a ghost ?
I was tricked into it .
After that I was always given ghost roles .
- You do look rather ghostlike . - What 's that supposed to mean ?
- lt 's agreed then . - Wait. I 'm not going to do it. idiot .
Nori ? Are you here already ? Why are you in the dark ?
Hey , Nori ?
Tomoka , it 's me .
Why didn 't you open up ?
Here I am .
What 's wrong ?
- Hey ! - What 's the matter ?
It 's not happening . You worry too much about it .
Wait a little longer . It usually happens at around half twelve .
- What time is it now , Tomoka ? - Just be quiet for a while , yeah ?
- Where is it ? Around here ? - Stop it , Nori .
You see. lt was there .
What is this ?
12 : 27 .
- This is a corner room , isn 't it ? - Yeah .
There is another reason why it 's called the haunted house .
A real reason .
Kyoko , there is more to this house than that .
There is another reason why it 's called the haunted house .
- And why is that ? - Sorry .
Actually ...
Oh. I 'm sorry .
This house was actually ... The family that lived there after the incident ...
Please record your message .
Hello , it 's Noritaka . I 'll come at around 1 1 again tonight .
Hello .
Hey ! Hello ...
What was that ?
What 's wrong with you ? Answer me if you 're there .
Are you still worried about it ?
- Hello . - Hello , Nori .
I 've just finished here on location .
Tomoka ?
I 'll come straight away . Hello , Nori ?
Hello ? Hello ?
Tomoka ?
Nori ?
Hey . Why 've you got the lights off ?
Megumi
- Sorry to have kept you waiting , Kyoko . - Please go ahead .
I 've seen all your movies .
Really ? Thank you .
One of them was really scary .
The one with the granny in a cupboard .
- The Cursed Sliding Screen ? - Yeah !
I saw that one too . It was scary .
Oh , really ? Thank you .
Kei . They brought it .
- Right. I 'm coming . - OK .
We 'll start from where you come in . You 're basically just following the reporter .
- Please comment in a cheerful way . - Yes .
To have the queen of horror movies in a haunted house makes for good TV .
What are you talking about ?
- Was somebody really murdered here ? - Yeah .
The newspapers wrote about it .
The woman who was killed in the first murder
is believed to continue to haunt the place .
What 's that ? Why do you keep on with it ?
- You 're ready now . - Thank you .
- Well , let 's go . - Yeah .
Hello . This is Miura Tomoka .
Today 's programme will focus on a house where murders have taken place .
The incident was covered by television and newspapers some years ago .
The abnormal events were the topic of those reports .
First of all , the woman who lived there was murdered by her husband .
Her body was found .
Then the couple 's son disappeared
and he still remains unaccounted for .
We are now entering the house where this incident took place .
We can see it now .
Narration . The title is in .
It 's in .
I 'm breathing this indescribable air .
This is the house in question .
I 'd now like to introduce our special guest .
She has starred in countless horror films and is known as the queen of horror .
It 's Harase Kyoko .
- Hello , Ms Harase . - Hello .
Yes , OK .
Kyoko . When you go into the house ,
stop and make it eerie .
There is more to this house than meets the eye .
It 's called a haunted house and there is a reason for that .
What reason ?
The people who moved in here after ,
and their relatives , have all died or disappeared .
Actresses are said to have strong intuition . Do you feel anything here ?
Well ...
There 's something about the atmosphere in this house that ...
- What were you doing ? - What 's wrong ?
It 's the microphone . Sorry .
The microphone ?
- What 's the matter ? - There was a strange sound .
- A sound ? - lt 's Ms Harase 's microphone .
Did you hear anything ?
- Are you imagining it ? - No , I really heard it .
- Couldn 't it be that somebody passed by ? - Let 's check .
- Did you really hear something ? - l 'm telling you I did .
I think you imagined it .
In a show like this it doesn 't matter anyway .
When you do horror films , do you go through ritual purification before filming ?
Yeah , generally .
But that 's not only for horror films .
I work a lot on documentaries about the supernatural
but I 've never been purified .
So that 's why you have all these amulets . It 's cute .
You 're easily scared , aren 't you ?
Hold on . What 's this one for ?
For Easy Childbirth
I 'll give it to you .
- Why ? - Aren 't you pregnant ?
- Why do you say that ? - lt 's obvious to another woman .
is it ?
- There you go . - Thank you .
I 'm a little disappointed . I thought it would be scarier .
Megumi , you 're into that kind of stuff . Did you feel anything in this house ?
What 's the matter with her ?
Megumi !
- lt could go either way . - Yeah . With his face all white .
- Right , Megumi ? - There 's nothing .
Nothing ? She wasn 't listening .
- People died here . - Oh ! Really ?
That .
I just noticed it. lt 's creepy .
Yeah. lt makes me feel uncomfortable .
I 've just finished here on location . Where are you now ?
Hello , Nori ? Hello ?
Thanks for your hard work .
- Thank you . - Thank you .
Oh ! Sorry , can you take care of this ?
- What is it ? I 'm locking up . - Sorry. I forgot something .
- l 'll be right back . - Don 't take too long .
Kayako
Hurry up , Megumi .
Tokunaga Katsuya Tokyo Nerima-Ku Kotobuki-Machi 4-8
That took you a while .
Did you find what you 'd forgotten ?
- Are you going to check the recording ? - Yeah .
- Tell me if there 's something on there . - Sure .
- Did you really hear something ? - With my own ears .
Good night .
What are you talking about ? I never heard of anything like that .
- Good night . - Night .
Actresses are said to have strong intuition . Do you feel anything here ?
Well ...
There 's something about the atmosphere in this house that ...
- Hey , what was that ? - What 's the matter ?
- lt 's the microphone . - The microphone ?
There was a strange sound there .
- lt 's from Ms Harase 's microphone . - What could it be ?
- Did you do something ? - No .
Are you sure you didn 't touch it ?
Let 's magnify it a bit .
Keisuke
Mum ?
Flowers wither so quickly .
Let me do it .
Masashi ! Masashi !
Masashi .
Hey , Masashi .
What shall I do ...
about our baby ?
I 'm confused .
Masashi ? What is it ?
What 's wrong ?
Masashi !
So , you had a traffic accident after leaving there ?
I got away with only slight injuries .
After that I couldn 't contact Tomoka , the reporter .
Two days later she was found in her flat .
Hanging by her neck next to her boyfriend .
What ?
According to the police , people connected with that location have died .
Then Megumi also went .
She went ?
I heard screams from the make-up room .
I ran there
but she was already dead .
How can this be ?
It 's not only those two .
I can 't get hold of Watanabe , the cameraman ,
or the sound recorder .
Don 't you think that 's strange ?
One after the other , the people who were on that location ...
My mother also passed away .
After that . Suddenly .
What ?
I 'm sorry , but I don 't want to get involved .
Megumi ?
Just now ?
It was Megumi . How ?
Megumi ?
Megumi !
You are Megumi , aren 't you ?
Keisuke .
- What 's that ? - Megumi left it .
What ?
is it a diary ?
I saw something just like it back in that house .
Eh ?
But why is it here ?
What is it ? What 's wrong ?
Will you come and help me ?
The Haunted House
Murder Of Wife
Missing
Wife Murdered At Home Husband Found Dead ln Street
Kayako .
Kayako
This woman wrote it .
After leaving the location , you were saved in your accident .
There has to be a reason .
I 'm going back to the house .
Wife Murdered Body Found ln Attic
Kayako
Toshio
Kyoko .
Hiromi ! Open up !
Hiromi !
Chiharu
- Hiromi . - You seem a little down .
Let me tell you about a fun job we can do .
My cousin works in films . She asked if I wanted to be an extra .
Let 's do it. lt 'll be fun ! Maybe we 'll meet some actors .
We 're cute , so they 'll probably use us .
Help !
Chiharu ? Are you all right ?
It 's our turn soon .
I had a strange dream .
Let 's go .
And cut !
You scared me . What 's wrong with you ? The script didn 't say scream .
You 're only an extra . Don 't do things you 're not told to do .
Chiharu ?
We 'll take a break and continue from scene 27 .
Hiromi .
Hiromi ! Please open up !
Hiromi ! Open up !
Hiromi ! Open the door ! Hiromi !
- Chiharu ! - Hiromi !
Chiharu ! Release the chain .
Hiromi !
I 'm so happy . She woke up .
Really ? is she all right ? Are you all right ?
- l 'm sorry about this . - Don 't worry .
She 's all right .
Chiharu . You were having a nightmare .
Help me , Hiromi . I have to get out of that house .
What house are you talking about ?
What happened ? Tell me about it .
You 've been acting very weird lately .
Hiromi , don 't do it . Don 't go to that house .
Don 't go in there .
What are you talking about ? Calm down and tell me . Chiharu !
Hey , Chiharu .
- Don 't come in . - Chiharu .
- Don 't come near me . - Stop it .
I won 't understand if you don 't tell me .
Chiharu , open up !
Answer me , Chiharu .
What 's happened , Chiharu ?
Hiromi , stop .
What 's happened ? Wake up !
Chiharu , what happened ?
Hiromi !
Kayako
Kyoko ! What 's happened ? Hang on .
Kyoko !
For Easy Childbirth
Do you know what it is ?
Blood pressure 96 over 60 . Rate 60 .
How is the lUFD flow ?
There , there .
- Deep breaths . - Prepare for emergency Caesarean .
Doctor , it 's already coming out .
What ?
The womb is shrinking. inject .
Mummy . Mummy ...
Bye . See you tomorrow .
Harase Kyoko : Sakai Noriko
Miura Tomoka : Niiyama Chiharu
Yamashita Keisuke : Horie Kei
Chiharu : Ichikawa Yui
Something that you 'd forgotten
Ties you up
Before you know it
You almost feel nothing
Slowly
A voice is calling my name
I hear it sometimes , but it cannot be
Because I was alone all the time
lt cannot be I am alone
lt 's enough now
lt 's enough
I can 't take any more
I don 't wish for any more
lf that time could come back
lt would be beautiful
It 's enough now
lt 's enough now
Now I can rest once again
lf that time could come back
lt would be beautiful